I am over here studying my tome.
I got ancient forbidden knowledge on my tome right now.
I'm just studying my tome.
I'm hunger for knowledge as fuck, man.
I am a dark wizard, man!
Dark castle full of freaks,
chained hoes on the leash,
Mixing’ dirty potions, I’m the plug for the streets.
Unlicensed, untaxed,
I’m the king of the fiends,
Monkey minions running’ wild,
makin’ noise for the team.
So when the moon’s blood red
and the night's alive,
You know who runs the night,
who makes the darkness thrive.
I’m the villain, I’m the wizard,
I’m the king of the block-
In this castle of sin, I got the keys and the lock.
Let your gaze not meet mine
lest you be slain in a ride-by,
bisected in twain by halberds
as I come galloping
through town.